Kirk Thompson

Electrical Engineer - The Boeing Company, Rotorcraft Division

Ridley Park, PA - Email me on Indeed: indeed.com/r/Kirk-Thompson/8b406dc4b2c96262

A technically challenging position as an Electrical Engineer where I can increase both my breadth and depth of Engineering knowledge and experience, and contribute to the learning of others.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Electrical Engineer

The Boeing Company, Rotorcraft Division - Ridley Park, PA - April 2003 to Present

Develop solutions to a wide range of technical problems applying motivation, process development, and self-direction. Served as site focal for V-22 Suite of Integrated Radio Frequency Countermeasures (SIRFC) cable testing. Functioned as Avionics Team liaison to production shop-floor personnel.

Developed in-depth test procedure for testing aircraft antennas prior to installation, leading to reduction of production removals. By testing the antennas in a controlled environment prior to installation, antenna performance was verified and to meet or exceed manufacturer's specification.

Electrical Specialist

Systra Consulting, Sept - Philadelphia, PA - June 2002 to April 2003

Solved Engineering problems using both an individual and team oriented approach. Functioned as project liaison and coordinator for New York City Metro-Transit Authority (LIRR Project) for the installation of their 3rd rail alarm system. The alarm system incorporated fiber-optic technology connected to Grand Central Station and terminated near the Connecticut cross-over

Technical Skills

Thorough knowledge of Microsoft Office Suite including Microsoft Project Engineering Applications: MathCAD, AutoCAD 2008/2010, Microsoft Visio Kirk Thompson, BSEE, MSEE, EIT, BSN

Registered Nurse BSN

St Vincent Home Care - Erie, PA - August 1997 to May 2000

Responsibilities

Provided one on one Nursing care to patients in their home, and managed other interdisciplinary (eg PT) appointments. Cases in included wound care, IV medication management, and patient teaching of all disease processes.

Accomplishments

As an adjunct, I led a team to develop education materials for our patients including medication

Skills Used

IV therapy

IV insertion technique

Patient assessment
IV pump maintenance
Wound care and stoma care
Diabetes teaching and management

Eagle Scout

Boy Scouts of America - 1987 to 1987 1987 emiguy@comcast.net 215-806-0135

EDUCATION

Master of Science in Electrical Engineering/Telecommunications

Widener University September 2003 to May 2007

Bachelor of Science in Electrical Engineering

Penn State University May 2002

Bachelor of Science in Nursing

West Chester University May 1995